



Javad **Haditaghi**Web Developer & Data Analyst

Mashhad, Iran

☑ javadht1990a@gmail.com

& +98 937-606-8193

SOCIAL

in @javad-haditaghi

@javad_haditaghi

Javad Haditaghi

PERSONAL INFO

DOB: 22 September 1990

Nationality: Iranian

PROFILE

A multidisciplinary researcher, as demonstrated by merging network theory with discourse analysis using Computational Linguistics, resulting in 1 publication in a peer-reviewed scientific journal

An eager data analyst who performed multiple analyses using deep learning and machine learning methods.

A highly qualified web developer striving to implement artificial intelligence techniques to enhance user experience and website performance.

An ambitious teacher and writer who has evaluated a significant number of teaching methods and writing techniques to apply in an academic environment

EDUCATION

M.A. IN ENGLISH TEACHING

From 2015 to 2018 | Guilan University

Supervised by Dr. Jaleh Hassaskhah

Thesis Title: A corpus linguistic approach to the study of the voices in the text in light of Laclau and Mouffe's discourse theory

*A synopsis of the work undertaken is attached here

B.A. IN ENGLISH TRANSLATION

From 2010 to 2014 |

PUBLICATIONS

A NETWORK-BASED APPROACH FOR DISCOURSE ANALYSIS FROM LACLAU AND MOUFFE'S PERSPECTIVES.

Haditaghi, J., Hassasskhah, J., & Sorahi, M. (2020). A network-based approach for discourse analysis from Laclau and Mouffe's perspectives. Journal of Computer-Assisted Linguistic Research, 4(1), 1-22.

Click for DOI

 SIGNIFIER, RELATION AND TEXT: A NETWORK-BASED APPROACH FOR SEMANTIC CONTENT ANALYSIS

Accepted but not published

TEST SCORES

TOEFL TEST SCORE

October 2022

Listening: 29 | Reading: 29 | Speaking: 25 | Writing: 30

Overal Score: 113

RESEARCH INTERESTS

Network Theory

• Machine Learning

• Computational Linguistics

Deep Learning

• Complex Theory

• Interdisciplinary Approaches

• Natural Language Processing

• Data Analysis

SKILLS

Programming

• HTML • Python

CSSPandas

Sass
Matplotlib

JavaScript
Numpy

JquerySeaborn

Bootstrap
Pytorch

ReactScikitlearn

OpenCV

Other Skills

Using Gephi
Content Writing

• Microsoft Office • Webscraping

EXPERIENCE

TEAM MANAGER | DEKA TEAM

Deka Team

2023 - NOW

Develop and implement a strategic roadmap for the integration of AI technologies into web development projects, ensuring alignment with company objectives and industry best practices.

WEB DEVELOPER & DATA ANALYST

Golden Nutrition LLC

2020 - Now

Conduct comprehensive data analysis to identify trends, patterns, and insights, leveraging statistical techniques and data mining tools to optimize business processes and drive informed decision-making.

WEB DEVELOPER

Freelancer

2018 - Now

Collaborate with clients to conceptualize, design, and implement intuitive user interfaces and responsive web applications, ensuring a seamless user experience as a freelance front-end developer.

ENGLISH TEACHER

Different Institutes in Mashhad

2012 - Now

Develop and deliver comprehensive English language lessons to students across various institutes in Mashhad, ensuring a dynamic and engaging learning environment.

CERTIFICATE

Programming with JavaScript (META)

This course helped me get a good understanding of the JS programming language.

Click here to see it on Coursera

HTML5 & CSS3 Complete Course: Build Websites like a Pro (Udemy)

In this course, I learned html and css ability to creat responsive and user friendly interfaces.

Click here to see it on Udemy

Python Programming (from MFT Mashhad)

In this course I tried to learn the basics of python programming

Advanced Python Programming (from MFT Mashhad)

In this course, I have tried to learn data analysis using machine learning and deep learning algorithms.

Web Design (MFT Mashhad)

In this course, I learned html, css, js, ajax and react to creat responsive and user friendly interfaces.

Web Design (MFT Mashhad)

In this course, I learned html, css, js, ajax and react to creat responsive and user friendly interfaces.

LANGUAGES

- Persian (Native)
- English (C2)
- German (A1)

INTERESTS

7

Classical Music

Travel

Reading

Conceptual Art

?

REFERENCES

Dr. Jaleh Hassaskhah (My M.A. thesis advisor)

Associate professor, Department of English Language & Literature

Guilan University, Rasht, Iran

Phone: 000-000-0000*

Email: jaleh_hassaskhah@yahoo.com

Dr. Abdorreza Tahriri (My M.A. thesis referee & course professor)

Associate professor, Department of English Language and Literature

Guilan University, Rasht, Iran

Phone: 000-000-0000* Email: atahriri@gmail.com

Dr. Mohammad Amin Sorahi (My M.A. thesis Co-Supervisor)

Assistant professor, Department of English Language and Literature

Guilan University, Rasht, Iran

Phone: 000-000-0000*

Email: aminsorahi@hotmail.com